{
results: [
{
category: ["orange", "yes", "yes", "probably"],
type: "boolean",
difficulty: "hard",
question: "Do I suck at coding?",
correct_answer: "orange",
incorrect_answers: [
"orange"
]
},
{
category: "Entertainment: Video Games",
type: "boolean",
difficulty: "hard",
question: "In thekjkjkjkjkj game &quot;Melty Blood Actress Again Current Code&quot;, you can enter Blood Heat mode in Half Moon style.",
correct_answer: "False", 
incorrect_answers: [
"True"
]
},
{
category: "General Knowledge",
type: "boolean",
difficulty: "hard",
question: "&quot;Number 16 Bus Shelter&quot; was a child&#039;s name that was approved by the New Zealand government.",
correct_answer: "True",
incorrect_answers: [
"False"
]
},
{
category: "Entertainment: Video Games",
type: "boolean",
difficulty: "hard",
question: "In Undertale, having a &quot;Fun Value&quot; set to 56-57 will play the &quot;Wrong Number Song Call&quot;.",
correct_answer: "False",
incorrect_answers: [
"True"
]
},
{
category: "Science: Computers",
type: "boolean",
difficulty: "hard",
question: "DHCP stands for Dynamic Host Configuration Port.",
correct_answer: "False",
incorrect_answers: [
"True"
]
},
{
category: "Entertainment: Music",
type: "boolean",
difficulty: "hard",
question: "The song &quot;Mystery Train&quot; was released by artist &quot;Little Junior&#039;s Blue Flames&quot; in 1953.",
correct_answer: "True",
incorrect_answers: [
"False"
]
},
{
category: "General Knowledge",
type: "boolean",
difficulty: "hard",
question: "In Scandinavian languages, the letter &Aring; means river.",
correct_answer: "True",
incorrect_answers: [
"False"
]
},
{
category: "Science: Mathematics",
type: "boolean",
difficulty: "hard",
question: "L&#039;H&ocirc;pital was the mathematician who created the homonymous rule that uses derivatives to evaluate limits with indeterminations.",
correct_answer: "False",
incorrect_answers: [
"True"
]
},
{
category: "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
type: "boolean",
difficulty: "hard",
question: "In the &quot;To Love-Ru&quot; series, Peke is considered a female robot.",
correct_answer: "True",
incorrect_answers: [
"False"
]
},
{
category: "General Knowledge",
type: "boolean",
difficulty: "hard",
question: "Spoon theory is a theory, utilizing &quot;Spoons&quot; as a metaphor for energy they can use in a day.",
correct_answer: "True",
incorrect_answers: [
"False"
]
}
]
}